我第一次见你的时候啊
别以为你就是朵人畜无害的小白花
简直是爱心泛滥过头了
才敢帮我捡回家
我当时浑身都挂着彩
头
皮都差点被人削下了一块
躺在那的时候
路过的几个大老爷们都绕着我走
都是你多云下来看了一会儿
竟然让我跟你回家
还要我说谢谢你不会那个时候就看上我了
蹲在那儿够量三围的吧
行怎么不行
能入您的法眼
不是我的福气吗
我们到底算什么关系啊
应该算不上是朋友吧
是
还是说我就是你喂过的一条流浪狗
那你让我怎么想
你对我招之即来
挥之即去
想见我的时候
我放下手里所有的事情来满足你的需求
如果不想见我
根本就找不到你
我不能对你提要求
如果让你觉得被束缚了
你随便就能狠下心
一个月不来找我
也从来没有说过喜
操真他妈矫情
好了再拐个弯就到了
今天我就不上去了
等会我帮你把车停好就直接回去了
什么
我是你的什么
猎人
哎我早就疯了
我今天可能坚持不了太久啊
姐姐
就这恋人是不是可以每天见面
每天一起吃早饭
吃午饭吃
我没想说服你
带着狗链子的
是我连我跟我见过吧
你走你的路
我只会在你身边跟着
不瞎练
我的手也可以把我关在家里
只要你记得我
我就行
委屈自己
敲响的时候或许会委屈
但只要见到你
我就变回了那条训练有素的狗
这块肉他们能高兴一点
真吓人啊
对不对
可我只会这样爱你
♪ You chain me up ♪
Still speculating never enough
♪ But ching and share the more rainbow ♪
慢慢吞
♪ 千万不 ♪
♪ Any moment ♪
♪ I'll have you begging me ♪
♪ Don't turn your back ♪
I can't you see that
♪ I'm addictable ♪
♪ I'm unmistakable ♪
♪ I'm hearing it all ♪
I hear it in my hand spirit
♪ Now ♪
♪ We're spit again ♪
♪ Caring it ♪
♪ Only shame ♪
I just ra if you breaking into you
♪ Keep calling me and say go got it in my head careful ♪
♪ What you shame think it might be right ♪
♪ Though you made me a psycho ♪
♪ A psycho ♪
♪ You keep calling me a psycho ♪
♪ So that i was scared ♪
♪ But i can't prepain think you might be right ♪
♪ Though you made me a psycho ♪
♪ A psycho ♪
♪ You made me a psycho ♪
♪ Psycho ♪
♪ You won't stop me in ♪
♪ Don't bother trying never enough ♪
♪ Cause you will see a rainbow ♪
♪ I'm uncontainable ♪
I always search for light and darkness
♪ You'll never think ♪
I'm wake
♪ Cause ♪
♪ I'm untainable ♪
I'm unmistakable
♪ I'm hearing it all ♪
♪ I hear it in my hand ♪
♪ Go spin and spirit again ♪
♪ Hearing it only shame ♪
I just re if you need to dance to you
Keep calling me a psycho
♪ Sin my head careful ♪
♪ What you shame take it might be way ♪
♪ So you made me a psycho ♪
♪ A psycho ♪
♪ You can call me a psycho ♪
♪ So that i was scared ♪
♪ But i came prepain ♪
♪ Think it might be right ♪
♪ Though you made me a shao ♪
♪ A shao ♪
♪ You made me a psycho ♪
♪ Psycho ♪
♪ Hearing it ♪
♪ All ♪
♪ I hear it in my head ♪
♪ Spin there with spirit again ♪
♪ Hearing it ♪
♪ All they see me ♪
♪ I should straight put your mickey ♪
Pushing to the edge
You keep calling me
♪ You say girl ♪
♪ Got it in my head ♪
♪ Careful ♪
♪ What you shame think it might be right ♪
♪ Though you may be a shackle ♪
♪ Shyle ♪
♪ You can call me a shako ♪
♪ Something that i was scared ♪
♪ But i came prepain thinking might be right ♪
♪ Though you made me a po a po ♪